<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on William Pansky | Dallas, TX</title>
    <link>/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on William Pansky | Dallas, TX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2017 William Pansky.</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>DNN website for the Dallas branch of national NPO, Goodwill Industries</title>
      <link>/projects/goodwilldallas.org/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/goodwilldallas.org/</guid>
      <description>Introduction For over 90 years Goodwill Dallas has been committed to providing job training and employment to those with disabilities and disadvantaging conditions.
As part of the creative department of Miller Ad Agency, we collaborated and worked to bring Goodwill Dallas the new life it came looking for.
Objective Establish and implement a new identity for Goodwill Dallas; a fresh look to update their brand and bring the Dallas branch, with it’s 15+ store locations, up to the modern age.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I organize my project assets; installable via Bower</title>
      <link>/projects/pansky-boilerplate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/pansky-boilerplate/</guid>
      <description>Installation If you&amp;rsquo;re a crazy person and, for some odd reason, want to download and tinker then be my guest. You can install with the Bower package manager.
bower install pansky-boilerplate --save  Primary tools - SCSS - Gulp - Babel - Babili - PostCSS - CSSnano - AutoPrefixer - Stylelint - Rename - SASS - SourceMaps - Util - Vinyl FTP  SCSS file structure I compartmentalize my SCSS partial files into the following structure:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress CMS platform built with Elementor Pro for Dallas full-service ad agency</title>
      <link>/projects/miller.agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/miller.agency/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Over the course of my third year at Miller Ad Agency I became increasingly infatuated with front-end web development.
I learned as much as I could, I dreamt about UI and UX before falling asleep, I carved out a (basically) web-only position for myself; if it were possible to eat web dev – I&amp;rsquo;d have probably done that too.
My awesome art director and good friend, Sasha Gelemanovic, knew he needed a way to keep me interested in the day-to-day workload.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress powered by WooCommerce for Dallas apparel boutique website</title>
      <link>/projects/illusiveapparel.website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/illusiveapparel.website/</guid>
      <description>Illusive Apparel delivers award-winning graphic artists create fresh and cutting edge designs.
Case study coming soon.
To view the demo site, click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wordpress website for Dallas gift wrapping artist, Anita Ivancevic</title>
      <link>/projects/giftwrapcreations.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/giftwrapcreations.com/</guid>
      <description>Case study coming soon.
To view the demo site, click here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>