<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on William Pansky | Dallas, TX</title>
    <link>/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on William Pansky | Dallas, TX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2017 William Pansky.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Respect My Pretty</title>
      <link>/portfolio/respect-my-pretty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/respect-my-pretty/</guid>
      <description> Shana Mcmillan approached me, thanks to a tip via our mutual friend Krystal René with an opportunity to go wild and create some really interesting and visually exciting t-shirt designs. Respect My Pretty is the movement &amp;rdquo;&amp;hellip;of girls, women demanding respect for our individuality as well as embracing the individuality of others-&amp;rdquo; and Shana really wanted to have that driven home in the art.
Speak No Ugly HANDSOME </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serendipitax</title>
      <link>/portfolio/serendipitax/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/serendipitax/</guid>
      <description>Collaboration with the same crew of Estranged, I was once again commissioned to create key art for the group’s, named 17 Productions, next indie short film. Serendipitax is about Michael’s chance to recruit an inmate to his side, but his own psychological paranoia taxed his potential to save her.
Photography by the talented Krystal Hills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Self-Titled EP</title>
      <link>/portfolio/tungsten-wake-ep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/tungsten-wake-ep/</guid>
      <description>Many years ago I created an album for a local band named Solcide; they loved the work. They enjoyed it so much that contacted me again, years later, and hired me to whip them up something new for their latest project - Tungsten Wake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evol World</title>
      <link>/portfolio/evol-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/evol-world/</guid>
      <description>Alex the Great&amp;rsquo;s original Evol World art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strangle and The Struggle EP</title>
      <link>/portfolio/the-strangle-and-the-struggle-ep/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/the-strangle-and-the-struggle-ep/</guid>
      <description>Monique Hernandez-Fuentes, an old friend of mine, presented me with the opportunity to design her EP album, The Strangle &amp;amp; the Struggle. You can listen to the entire EP for free online at SoundCloud and purchase the physical copy at StoreEnvy.
Cover art by Lango Oliveira.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Struggle EP</title>
      <link>/portfolio/the-struggle-ep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/the-struggle-ep/</guid>
      <description>Tungsten Wake, man; they hit me up again! This time for a single ep release they had coming out soon. I love the final turnout of this one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>